Boosting, as we saw before,
Boosting （提升算法）
is a bit more elaborate.
会稍复杂一点
There are a few ways to do it but one of the most popular is
Boosting 算法有很多种
this algorithm ADABOOST discovered by Freund and Schapire in 1996.
其中最流行的是Freund 和 Schapire 在1996年发明的ADABOOST 算法
Here's the gist of it.
尽管稍后
Although we'll develop the math in a bit more detail later.
我们会讲到一些数学细节 但这里是要点
I must say, if you look at it in the literature,
如果仅从字面看,
you may find it a bit different, but I promise you,
会有点不同 但我保证
aside from trivial things like multiplying all the waste by constants,
除了一些微不足道的事情 例如用常量乘以所有的剩余
which won't change the outcome,
但这不会改变结果
what I'll be showing you is the exact same ADABOOST algorithm.
我将要讲述的是一个完全相同的ADABOOST算法
The idea is the following, we fit our first learner in order to maximize accuracy,
想法如下 我们先拟合第一个学习器 来最大化准确度
or equivalently, minimize the number of errors.
或者最小化错误数量
There's a few good ones, but one can check that we can do no better than three errors.
有一些好的 但我们最多只能犯三个错误
So, let's fit it, and this is the model.
就是这个模型 让我们来拟合它
We'll remember this model for later.
我们先保存这个模型
Now, our second learner needs to fix on the mistakes that this one has made.
现在 我们的第二个弱学习器要修正第一个学习器的错误
So, what we'll do is we'll take the misclassified points, and make them bigger.
我们把第一个模型（弱学习器）误分类的点放大
In other words, we'll punish the model more if it misses these points.
换句话说 就是如果第二个模型漏掉这些误分类点 就加大惩罚
So, the next weak learner needs to focus on these more.
所以 下一个弱学习器需要更多地关注这些误分类的点
Our second weak learner will be this one,
这是第二个弱学习器
which correctly classifies these points.
它正确分类了这些点
We'll remember this one for later.
我们保存这个模型
Now again, we punish the points that are misclassified by this one,
现在 我们再次惩罚这个错误分类的点
by enlarging these points over here.
把这些点放大
Our third weak learner is this one,
这是第三个弱学习器
which tries really hard to correctly classify the big points. We'll remember this one.
它会更努力的尝试对大点进行正确的分类我们保存这个模型
Now, we can keep going,
我们可以继续重复这个过程
but let's say three is enough.
但假设三个就够了
Now, we want to combine these models,
现在 我们要组合这些弱学习器模型
and I'll be more specific about combining them later,
以后  我会更具体的讲一下怎样组合它们
but for now let's imagine that we're making them vote like before.
现在 先让我们假设让它们象以前一样举行投票
So, our resulting model is this,
所以 这个就是我们拟合数据后
which one we fit in the data,
得到的模型
we realize it fits it very well.
它拟合的非常好
So, as I said, I was a bit vague on the details,
在这节课 我没有讲太多细节
let me be more specific in the next few videos.
我们将在接下来的几个视频中讲更具体的细节